# **Areegbe David Oluwaseun**

**BACKEND DEVELOPER** 

### **CONTACT INFORMATION**

ADDRESS: FLAT B BEHIND RECTEM MULTIPURPOSE HALL REDEMPTION CAMP MOWE OGUN STATE NIGERIA

PHONE NUMBER: +2349015061171

EMAIL: davidcodes2005@gmail.com

GITHUB: <a href="https://github.com/davidcodes17">https://github.com/davidcodes17</a>

### **OBJECTIVE**

Backend developer with 5+ years of leading terms and delivering high-quality software on time and within budget. Key goal: Writing long lasting, platform independent and reliable code, I would like to work with you and help you convert your ideas to possibilities.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JAVA SE, SPRING BOOT, REACT JS, SQL, MONGODB, INTELLIJE IDEA, VISUAL STUDIO CODE, NETBEANS, MS OFFICE.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **GODSOFT SYSTEMS LIMITED**

PROGRAMMING INSTRUCTOR (2017 - 2020)

WORKED AS A PROGRAMMING INSTRUCTOR RASING YOUNG DEVELOPER WITH DIFFERENT PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES AND SOFTWARE PACKAGES LIKE HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, JAVA, PYTHON, REACT JS, MSOFFICE, ETC

### **GODSOFT SYSTEMS LIMITED**

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (2021 - PRESENT)

WORKED AS A SOFTWARE DEVELOPER BUILDING LONG LASTING, PLATFORM INDEPENDENT AND RELIABLE SOFTWARES WHICH WERE SOLD TO OTHER BUSINESS ORGANISATIONS AND ALSO WAS IN USE IN THE ORGANISATION

# **EDUCATION**

# WEST AFRICAN EXAMINATION COUNCIL (WAEC)

KINGDOM MODEL COLLEGE (NIGERIA) (2019 - 2022)

### OND COMPUTER SCIENCE

THE REDEEMERS COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY AND MANAGEMENT (RECTEM)(2023 - PRESENT)

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

WEB DEVELOPER BY NEW HORIZONS (2020)

SCRATCH AND APP INVENTOR BY NEW HORIZONS (2021)

JAVA CERTIFIED BY GODSOFT SYSTEMS LIMITED (2021)

### **SOFT SKILLS**

- TEAM WORK
- PROBLEM SOLVING
- COMMUNICATION
- LEADERSHIP
- ADAPTABILITY

# **REFRENCES**

# **ENOCH OLUJUDE.A**

CEO GODSOFT SYSTEMS LIMITED

# **MORONKE TITILAYO.A**

CEO OLOBE CLASSIK
MANAGING DIRECTOR GODSOFT SYSTEMS LIMITED

# **OLUWASEUN EMMAUEL**

**CEO ALHERI'S COLLECTIONS**